Jovannie M. Lozano

Dear Sir/ Madam,

Good morning, I'm writing this letter in reference to the open post at your company. I am hard-working, honest, trustworthy, reliable, willing and humble person.

I am very ambitious, persuasive and great public relation skill and personality. I want to help the company to continue to grow and offer a better service and advertising for the community. I have learned a lot of vital information, skill and discipline in the years of working.

In closing this letter, a copy of my resume is present; giving a profile that entails my education and previous background experiences. Thank you for the time you took out of your busy schedule to review my application.

Kind Regards,

Jovannie M. Lozano

Jovannie Lozano

(501) 620 7999/ (501) 611-1611

jovannielozano89@gmail.com

D.O.B: September 24th, 1989

Objective To become a part of your team within the company providing a service for our country. Working with others or a team is most rewarding to me with emphasis. Learning different ethnicity, culture and background to uplift our country.

Education

Pre-School: Lloyd Coffin Pre-School

Primary School: All Saints' School – Graduated 2002 – Certificate

Secondary: Wesley College - Graduated 2006 - Diploma

Tertiary: Wesley Junior College- Graduated 2015- Associate Degree in Information Technology

Experiences

Young's Electrical Maintenance Group- 1 Year (2003-2004)

Primary Objective

Maintenance worker (electrical, plumbing, etc.)

Belize Telemedia Limited- 2 years (2004-2006)

Primary Objective

Casual Worker (Sideman, in office work)
Grace Kennedy Limited- 1 year (2007-2008)
Primary Objective
Warehouse Assistant
Bak-A-Bush Adventure Tours (Chukka)- 1 year (2008-2009)
Primary Objective
Cave (and Canopy) Tour Guide (Lead Guide)
Atlantic Insurance Limited- 8 years (2009 - 2017)
Primary Objective
Sales Account Executive Officer
Bla'k Royalty (January 2018 - February 2019)
Primary Objective
Manager/ Owner
Ferguson Digital Images (March 2019 - July 2019)- Temp.
Primary Objective
Photographer and Editor, Graphic Designer
Bowen & Bowen Co Ltd. (July 2019 - August 2019)
Primary Objective
Temporary Sales Assistant

Hakim Fine Dining (November 2019 to December 2019)

Primary Objective

Temporary Line Cook

Chukka Adventures (December 2019 to March 2020) (July 21 to January 2023)

Primary Objective

Bartender/ Sales Assistant

PulseISM (April 2020 to March 2021)

Primary Objective

Sales Accounts Manager

Ivinex (April 2021 to January 2022)

Primary Objective

Sales Account Executive

Office Equipment:

I can operate the following machinery: Phone, Computer (All Microsoft software (word, excel, Power point, etc.)),Fax-Machine, Photocopier

Language Spoken: English and a little Conversational Spanish

Other Interest: Dancing, Music, Writing, Reading, Travelling, Graphic design

Goal: To achieve more knowledge, advance in life and to be a respectable and accountable hard-working person, to become a successful worker and family man.